ISAIAH GOODRIDGE







isaiahgood17@gmail.com | \$\&\sum_{347-652-8638}\$ | in https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaiahgood



https://github.com/IsaiahGoodridge?tab=repositories

CERTIFICATIONS

Meta - Front-End Developer Professional Certificate | October 2023

SKILLS

Programming - Javascript, React, Node.js, HTML, CSS

Code Editing & Version Control - Visual Studio Code, Git, GitHub

Design Tools - Figma

Soft Skills - Problem-Solving, Teamwork, Communication, Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Time Management

PROJECTS

Little Lemon Restaurant

https://tinyurl.com/Isaiah-Little-Lemon

Little Lemon Restaurant's website is a single-page application that allows users to utilize its booking form to reserve a table, which is connected to an API that fetches available times based on the date selected. The website was crafted with the core principles of UI/UX design in mind and the agility of a single-page application. Built with React.js, HTML, and CSS

Personal Website

https://isaiahgoodridge.github.io/personal-website-1/

Isaiah Goodridge's personal website provides information about his personal journey into web development as well as his top, up-to-date projects and technologies learned. Isaiah's website takes a modern, clean approach to building a page that is informative, easy to navigate, and uses satisfying animations to provide the user with an enjoyable experience that is not distracting from the main content. Built with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Medical Scribe

11/2019 - Present

Summit Health CityMD Urgent Care | Brooklyn, NY

Quality Assurance Specialist

06/2018 - 10/2019

ScribeAmerica | Brooklyn, NY, Hybrid

Medical Scribe

06/2017 - 06/2018

ScribeAmerica | Brooklyn, NY

EDUCATION